Vengeance is overdue.
Hell Hath No Fury is a action, war film directed by Jesse V. Johnson.
Branded a traitor by her countrymen, French national Marie DuJardin is rescued by American soldiers on one condition:
to survive, she must lead them to a cache of gold - before the Nazis return to claim it for themselves.
Marie, played by Nina Bergman.
Von Bruckner, played by Daniel Bernhardt.
Major Maitland, played by Louis Mandylor.
Jerry, played by Timothy V. Murphy.
Clement, played by Dominique Vandenberg.
Vic, played by Josef Cannon.
Nina Bergman is a Danish actress, singer, songwriter, and model.
She appeared in the films Doom: Annihilation, Cold Meat, and Chief of Station.
She was the lead singer in the band Letters from the Fire.